<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on London &amp; Newcastle</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on London &amp; Newcastle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>W.D. Snodgrass and Schweickart&#39;s Dual Hermeneutic</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-02-03-w-d-snodgrass-and-schweickarts-dual-hermeneutic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-02-03-w-d-snodgrass-and-schweickarts-dual-hermeneutic/</guid>
      <description>In my last post, I briefly examined Schweickart’s dual hermeneutic that can be applied to androcentric texts. In today’s post, I want to apply that theory to a cycle of confessional poetry by W.D. Snodgrass. This poetry is not usually considered to be ideologically problematic, particularly because confessional poetry links the speaker of the poem and the poet so closely and because the emotional anguish and vulnerability of the poetry tend to lead the reader to believe that this poetry speaks to a universal human condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matrixial Borderspaces Part 2 - South African Cinema</title>
      <link>/posts/matrixial-borderspaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/matrixial-borderspaces/</guid>
      <description>For my dissertation for my undergraduate degree, I decided to look into South African films. I chose Sink (Innes 2015) and Tsotsi (Fudakowski 2005). Sink is a relatively recent, independent film that revolves around 2 female protagonists, while Tsotsi is a mainstream film that won an Academy Award in 2005 and a Golden Globe in 2006.
Before I began my research, I watched as many South African films as I could, including Noem My Skollie, Dis Ek Anna, Ayanda, to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Body without Organs and Aronofsky&#39;s Black Swan</title>
      <link>/posts/body-without-organs-and-black-swan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/body-without-organs-and-black-swan/</guid>
      <description>We have an essay due for our critical theory module this semester and I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a topic that looks at deconstruction.
This is the title:
The idea of the self as a fixed entity is challenged by deconstruction and poststructural feminism. Explore the potential offered by the fragmentation of the self via discussion of these theories.
For a separate module we had studied The Body without Organs (Deleuze and Guattari 2004) and I knew that I somehow wanted to incorporate this into my essay on poststructuralism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 17:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi and welcome to London &amp;amp; Newcastle!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on my undergraduate thesis, and I got chatting to my supervisor about academic blogs. She was saying that reliable academic blogs are certainly a good source, and it&amp;rsquo;s important for Academia in general to remain up to date with changes in technology. Of course, this is not to say that journals, books, and printed articles are going to be replaced, but simply that academic blogs can also be useful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>