<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>London &amp; Newcastle on London &amp; Newcastle </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 15:44:36 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts Online!</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-11-08-podcasts-on-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 15:44:36 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-11-08-podcasts-on-apple/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally managed to get my first episode up and running on Apple Podcasts and Stitcher. Click here for more.
The sound in the first two episodes isn&amp;rsquo;t great but hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to sort that out in the next ones!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 09:19:01 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact
Feel free to contact me about submissions, joining a podcast episode or anything else at alessiazuccarelli at gmail dot com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasts</title>
      <link>/podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 23:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Podcasts
All of the London &amp;amp; Newcastle podcast episodes are available here.
 Academic podcasts that I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article on News 24</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-11-26-article-on-news-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:54:47 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-11-26-article-on-news-24/</guid>
      <description>As part of my undergraduate research I&amp;rsquo;ve written an article about cinema in South Africa and the important role it plays in shaping identity.
This was for an interdisciplinary seminar, and alongside this piece I wrote an academic essay as well. I have done a lot of research into cinema and representation on the big screen this year, and I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to do more research in this area once I&amp;rsquo;ve graduated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Body without Organs and Aronofsky&#39;s Black Swan</title>
      <link>/posts/body-without-organs-and-black-swan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/body-without-organs-and-black-swan/</guid>
      <description>We have an essay due for our critical theory module this semester and I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a topic that looks at deconstruction.
This is the title:
The idea of the self as a fixed entity is challenged by deconstruction and poststructural feminism. Explore the potential offered by the fragmentation of the self via discussion of these theories.
For a separate module we had studied The Body without Organs (Deleuze and Guattari 2004) and I knew that I somehow wanted to incorporate this into my essay on poststructuralism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 17:17:29 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi and welcome to London &amp;amp; Newcastle!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on my undergraduate thesis, and I got chatting to my supervisor about academic blogs. She was saying that reliable academic blogs are certainly a good source, and it&amp;rsquo;s important for Academia in general to remain up to date with changes in technology. Of course, this is not to say that journals, books, and printed articles are going to be replaced, but simply that academic blogs can also be useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 10:14:10 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to London &amp;amp; Newcastle
A blog dedicated to literature, critical theory, and all things academic.
My name is Alessia Zuccarelli and I am an Arts student at WIT in Waterford, Ireland. I&amp;rsquo;m majoring in English with Religion as my minor.
The purpose of this blog is to aid me in developing my thoughts around topics that I&amp;rsquo;m interested in or working on. Hopefully, it will be of help to someone doing research in a similar area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

